Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never ending,
so let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake
up, heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have traveled
different paths, we are best friends!
Our freedom is our only
compass that's pointing
us along the many roads
that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon,
we'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
And the whistle is reading
where we should be going. Go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is calling out, so ride away.
We're all together as one,
so let's stay with us done.
All our dreams are never ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up.
Heartbeat, we will be one of no hands!
My darkness will swallow the world!
Just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel
farther than we've ever gone.
And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And
then commence to live out
another day so intense
That's right, we're shining.
Running forever. Let's go along
with curiosity. Our feelings lead
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
Our minds will never give up. There's a
fire in our dreams. And you can never,
never, never, never stop
it We will be one, go ahead
What?
Don't look down,
ladies and gents But the
other competitors are flying
all over the place What's
causing such a phenomenon?
Kelly Funk is punching
them into a malignion
Rampage!
Now what's next?
I know what I saw, but I can't
make heads or tails of it
Did Bobby and Kelly become
one and the same somehow?
Jacket, jacket!
Two in a coat!
Bobby's been strong as hell
since the day he was born.
But all that muscle's
wasted on a softie like him.
That's where my power comes in handy.
When he wears me as his skin,
I can take over his body.
Then I bust out my
fighting skills and use his
brute strength in ways he
don't have the guts to.
I'm the guy who ate the
jacket jacket fruit.
It lets me take control
of any man or any beast
that puts me on and
wears me like a jacket.
And since Bobby's wearing me,
we're just like the same person.
How about that?
He really made quick work of him.
Ah, so you must be the other
brother from the Kano kingdom.
Bad news, pal, your little bro
here didn't put up much of a fight.
Bobby and I make a pretty good
living working together as assassins.
But you, what a pity.
You can't even protect each other.
You beat him, because
he didn't train enough.
Ooh, that's harsh.
For a rampage!
Is this supposed to be the
great Kano Kingdom martial art?
Don't make me laugh! No,
I gave up any emotional
attachment to my brother
the moment I became a student
of the Aiden Pack Fist.
That said...
Upon my honor as the 13th leader
of the proud Haposui army,
I swear I will avenge
my fallen subordinates!
That. Was. Such. A. Thrill!
The eight impact fist claims its victim.
I can see why size the G and just when it
looked like no one would
beat that monster Kelly.
I still want my helmet back!
Charitable donations!
You've made me quite a wealthy man
over the past two years, you know.
I have? That's right.
I've made a fortune nabbing all the
prisoners you set free from Impel Down.
And I'm not giving up till
I've got the rest of you two.
The genius jester, Buggy.
First son of the sea, Jinbe.
Sir Crocodile.
The miracle maker, Ivankov.
Shiryu of the rain.
I'll be a hero for
hunting all of you down!
Oh yeah, I wonder how
those guys are doing?
And it's not just you.
There are even more escapees from level 6!
Ones the public doesn't even know about.
From level 6?
Right, and I know just where to find them
Guess some of the others made it out, too.
Damn it. Hold still.
Oops.
Give me that.
How dare you!
That hurts, you fool!
He's out of the ring!
Jean the Bandit has just been
defeated with a single blow!
Boy,
I'd hate to be on the receiving end of a
headbutt from the legendary
pirate Don Chinchou!
He's still got it!
And all the while,
two other tough competitors have been
locked in their own deadly battle!
This is an excellent matchup!
It's a life or death struggle.
Between two of the fiercest fighters.
ever to grace this day.
They blow down every competitor.
That stood in their way!
all in preparation for this struggle.
This is the true test of their skill.
Take it down.
The girls go wild with excitement.
everyone in the coliseum's got
their eyes glued to this one fight.
there's nowhere left to run—you will
answer for what your grandfather did,
Straw Hat luffy.
i'll make certain of that,
thanks to that bastard,
i lost my entire fortune and
everything that i once held dear.
my power, even my most precious
memories from the years
of my youth—I told you to take
it up with my grandpa, not me.
death is much too lenient.
a punishment for all the
suffering garb has made me
endure—I'll show him what
it means to live with loss.
that's a fate worse than
death. now surrender!
let's go.
I have to win this thing, no matter what.
and to do that, i have
to get through this guy.
i'm getting my revenge right
here and now—out of the way.
move aside.
a clash of conquerors!
hockey—this is what it
means to be a true king.
to be a true king
What, Boa Hancock,
is down to two competitors!
The arena has been
completely littered with
the unconscious bodies
of once mighty warriors,
all thanks to the clashing wills
of these final two fighters.
But it begs the question,
what did we just witness?
Yeah, so you wield the
Conqueror's Haki as well.
But what sort of king could
you ever hope to be, huh?
King of the Pirates.
What a bunch of rubbish.
Don't you know there are countless souls
in the new world who can wield such power?
The only way to determine who deserves
the title is a battle amongst you all.
And at the end of it,
you'd find the strongest warrior
amongst a legion of conquerors.
Only then could one be
called King of the Pirates.
Now tell me before I kill
you, who taught you Haki?
Rayleigh did.
So he's still alive.
How irksome?
Enough talk!
I'm sick of dredging up the past!
Whaaaaat?
Give me back my treasure, Scrawl-Hat!
Indeed, I may gaze upon its splendor,
but it lies forever waiting,
just beyond my reach, so close
yet so far, a living hell!
What's going on?
It appears this legendary pirate
is calling his eyes out!
Sai, I thought the plan was
for you to win the match.
I wasn't worthy enough
to move to the finals.
But trust me, once Grandpa gets
going, no one can stand in his way.
They called me Chinjow
the Drill because at one
time my head possessed
an extraordinary shape.
And so I ask you,
do you have any clue what pain Garp
inflicted on me for the millionth time?
How should I know?
Take him out, Lucy,
now's your chance, huh?
Oh, it's, sir, Luffy!
Why can't that boy ever seem to
keep his nose out of trouble?
All right, Sanji, I say—we
go to the Toy House,
rescue Congeno, and deal
with this situation later.
And I want to help you with that,
but I'm afraid it's gonna
have to wait—tons of marines!
Looks like they're trying to surround
the coliseum—so many to what end?
Seems like there's
an issue of pirates and criminals
openly competing in the tournament.
The Navy's gonna scoop them up
as soon as they leave the arena.
Well, a society
can only properly operate if
criminals are apprehended.
You do realize
you're working with pirates and
one of them is standing right here?
Oh yes!
here oh yes Forgive me.
We have to find some way to warn
Luffy about the situation out here.
But the entrance gate is so heavily
guarded, there's no way we can get in.
What are you all doing standing around?
You mean to tell me not a single contestant
has left the Coliseum? No, sir. Not yet.
I find that hard to believe, since there
were hundreds of losers from Block A and B.
They should have already
poured out by now.
It's very strange.
Vice Admiral Maynard went
undercover as a competitor,
but we haven't been able to contact him.
He just had to charge in on his own.
A rookie mistake.
Whatever's going on inside, it's got
the stench of corruption all over it.
There are two special
laws here in Dressrosa.
Rules that have been strictly observed
since Doflamingo's reign began a decade ago.
First, there's a kingdom-wide
curfew at midnight.
No citizen is allowed
outside after 12. What?
Not even grown-ups?
Humans have to return to their homes.
And toys back to the house of toys.
No one is allowed outside late at night.
Not even to go out and buy a drink?
Everything's closed anyway.
Second rule.
Toys must not enter human houses, and
humans are to never enter a toy house.
That's crazy!
Looks like everyone's
friendly with each other,
so I don't get why
there's a law against it.
But I guess there's gotta be some kind
of distinction between people and toys.
Though anywhere else, I
would go without saying.
I've only been here a little while.
but really, I've gotten
used to things here already.
What kind of toys are you guys, though?
It's kind of confusing.
You have free will and can talk.
I mean, whoever created you all would
have to be some sort of genius like Dr.
Vegabuck.
Somebody!
Call the police!
What's going on?
Please, let go of me!
Esther, it's me!
It's got human on us!
This toy's broken!
Don't you recognize my voice, Esther?
Why don't you remember who I am?
I'm not a toy!
Stay away, you disgusting little creep!
What's your issue?
You've never acted like this around her.
Please remember me, Esther!
Get away from her, you freak!
You're coming with us.
Damn it!
My Esther!
How can you forget your
boyfriend so quick?
I beg you, you don't hook
up with that bastard!
You know who I am!
Let go of me!
No!
No, don't!
This is absurd!
Unhand me, you fiends!
I'm a human!
Give me a ride, Onepoco! Not a chance!
You're way too heavy for me!
I'll have a word with him. Don't worry.
about him he's a toy just like us well
tell him who
you are I'm the
father of that boy over there
That woman with him is my wife.
My name is Milo, not one Poco.
Young man, is your father around?
Nuh-uh.
I never had one, sir.
May I ask if you have a husband? I don't.
You see, I never married.
Uh, is that so unusual?
Bye!
A soldier?
What were you trying to prove
to me back there with the dog?
What's going on here?
Simple.
This kingdom's divided.
A country filled with the forgotten,
and those who forget them.
Every toy you see was
at one point a human.
What?!
Someone came to our island ten
years ago, courtesy of Doflamingo.
They turned us into toys
with their Devil Fruit power.
Wait, if you're a toy,
that means look—we're
approaching flower field!
I'll tell you everything once we arrive.
No
mercy for the wicked.
It'd be quicker if I wasn't a thun.
Thun. What are
you waiting for, Nami?
You were attacked, weren't you?
It's useless, Haki!
We need tension rods to keep all
the shelves from falling down.
Say, Leo, you should get going soon.
Do you need a lunch?
Thanks, Grandma, but I'm sure there'll
be something to eat over at headquarters.
If you're sure.
Careful!
I know.
I'm going to sew everything
that might fall over.
There!
Safety's been restored!
Boy, that Usalund sure
is something, isn't he?
So much power, he can shake the entire
kingdom only using that strange old Haki.
That's right!
Because Usalund's a hero
straight out of the legends!
Oh, and by the way, Leo, I know I look
old, but I'm not going to topple over.
So this is Tomtada Kingdom.
What kind of relationship
do you think these
guys have with the
warlord Doflamingo anyway?
No clue, but I know they're
dead serious about fighting him.
Hey there, Usalind and Robbalind!
Have you two gotten enough to eat?
Oh, yeah, I totally pigged out.
Uh, that is, I am full
and ready for action!
See, what did I tell you?
My body's trembling
with so much excitement,
it's making the Earth shake all around us!
Whoa!
How awesome is that?
His power is off the charts.
One question, Leo.
Your people keep mentioning some final
battle involving yours truly. But...
what reason do you want
to fight Doflamingo? Huh?
Not just a hero, but a comedian, too.
Because we want to rescue
500 of our closest friends.
Over in the secret factory in Dressrosa.
where they're being enslaved, of course.
What?
Did you say a factory?
You mean the one Luffy and
the others want to destroy?
Hey, wait a minute.
The same one that's producing Smile?
I don't know what they're being
forced to manufacture there,
but they've imprisoned
an important tentata.
Our obnoxious, selfish,
fickle, despicable,
mean-spirited Princess Monchery
is being held inside that plant.
So we've got to hurry. Yeah?
The way you describe her
makes her sound kind of awful.
Oh, she is.
But she's still one of us.
And Nolan himself would rescue anyone
who needed saving, wouldn't he?
What? Right!
That's totally what a real hero would do!
I mean, I am his descendant, after all!
Let's hear it for our legendary hero!
Leo! Flopper!
I heard the Don Quixote
family is leaving the palace!
Probably beneath the Coliseum!
The Yellow Cobbis and Beyond's pink
bees are ready to fly any time!
Understood!
Let's move out, Usaland and Roboland! Huh?
Are the rest of you Tontadas ready to go?
Our fight is in Dressrosa!
Beneath the Coliseum, inside the Factory!
Everyone, go!
Yeah!